{"data":[{"question":"In towns, there was very few bus shelters until about thirty years ago.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Communication","b":"will","c":"if","d":"his","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Will-> would","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Most people no longer wears the kinds of clothes that protect them from the wind, cold and rain.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"more","b":"know","c":"most","d":"can","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Most-> more","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Most of them were build in the nineteenth century and some are very grand.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"things","c":"using","d":"what","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Using->use","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"They were intended to persuade people to drink water, instead with beer or spirits.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"well","b":"with","c":"also","d":"talking","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Talking-> talk","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Communication will be impossible if everyone made up his own language.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"her","b":"to show","c":"have","d":"disagreement","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Her->their","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"The more words you know, the most ideas you can express.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Written","b":"of","c":"is","d":"to follow","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Of->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Words are the main things we using in communicating what we want to say.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"use","b":"and","c":"emphasizing","d":"make","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Emphasizing-> to emphasize","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"As well as talking with our voices we can also talking with our bodies.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"between","b":"roles","c":"no longer","d":"clearly","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Clearly-> clear","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Written language without of punctuation is not easy to follow.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"change","b":"dressed","c":"the","d":"make","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Dressed-> dress","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"We use volume and pitch emphasizing words and make meanings clear.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"who","c":"for","d":"and","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- For-> with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"}]}